reqcloud.com 2016-10-13

# Privacy | Social Recruiting and Employer Branding

* * *

ReqCloud, Inc ("ReqCloud") is committed to protecting your privacy. We have prepared this Privacy Policy to describe to you our practices regarding the Job Data and Personal Data (each as defined below) that we collect from users of our website (located at www.reqcloud.com), the ReqCloud RPM products (the "Products"), or related services. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and considered a part of, the ReqCloud Terms of Service, currently located at www.reqcloud.com/terms.

This Privacy Policy covers our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website and service at www.reqcloud.com. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged ReqCloud.

ReqCloud complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/.

User Consent

By submitting or making available Job Data or Personal Data through our website, Products, or related services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and you expressly consent to the processing of your Job Data and Personal Data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Your Personal Data may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in other countries, including the United States, where laws regarding processing of Personal Data may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

Information We Collect About You

Types of Data We Collect

ReqCloud collects Personal Data and Anonymous Data from you when you visit our site, when you send us information or communications, and/or when you download and use our Products. "Personal Data" means data that allows someone to identify or contact you, including, for example, your name, phone number, zip code, and e-mail address. "Anonymous Data" means data about you that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Data (but does not include Job Data, which is covered later in this Privacy Policy); Anonymous Data does not permit the identification of individual persons. We collect Personal Data and Anonymous Data, as described below.

Personal Data You Provide to Us

We collect Personal Data from you, such as first and last name, phone number, zip code, e-mail, professional title, company name, and password, when you purchase Products, register to receive information, or post information anywehere on our website. In addition, we (or our third-party credit card or payment processor on our behalf) will collect Personal Data including your credit card number or account information when you purchase Products or services on our website. We also retain information on your behalf, such as the Personal Data described above and any correspondence or blog comments. If you provide us feedback or contact us via e-mail (e.g., in response to an employment opportunity posted on our website), we will collect your name and e-mail address, as well as any other content included in the e-mail, in order to send you a reply, and any information that you submit to us, such as a resume. When you submit information, such as a job application in response to a job posting, this information is provided to both ReqCloud as well as the hiring manger or recruiters who posted the job on RqCloud website and/or advertised it using ReqCloud or another service on another wibsite. When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional profile information such as your name, phone number, address, and e-mail address. We also collect other types of Personal Data that you provide to us voluntarily, such as operating system and version, information about your application and operating environment, and other requested information if you contact us via e-mail regarding support for the Products). We may also collect Personal Data at other points in our website that state that Personal Data is being collected.

Personal Data Collected via Technology

To make our website, Products, and related services more useful to you, our servers (which may be hosted by a third-party service provider) collect Personal Data from you, such as browser type, operating system, Internet Protocol (IP) address (a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet, which may vary from session to session), domain name, and/or a date/time stamp for your visit. We may also use Cookies (as defined below) and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and which you viewed. Like most Internet services, we automatically gather this Personal Data and store it in log files each time you visit our website or access your account on our network.

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that a website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing a web site. We link the information we store in cookies to the personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. We may use both session Cookies (which expire once you close your web browser) and persistent Cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them) to provide you with a more personal and interactive experience on our website. Persistent Cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. If you choose to disable Cookies, some areas of our website may not work properly.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our [partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers] use session ID cookies to improve the quality of experience when you interact with our website, Products, and related services.

Our third party advertising partner employs a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information.

We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

We use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to serve you video content. Third Parties, with whom we partner to provide these features on our site, use Flash cookies to collect and store information.

Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here.

Personal Data Collected by Third Parties

We may receive Personal Data about you from other sources like telephone or fax, from companies that provide our Products or services by way of a co-branded or private-labeled website, companies that offer their products and/or services on our website, or companies that provide services (such as payment processing services) in connection with our website ("Partner Companies"). Our Partner Companies may supply us with Personal Data, such as your name and e-mail and mailing address information, in order to help us establish the account or fulfill orders.

Except as otherwise expressly provided in this Privacy Policy, only ReqCloud collects Personal Data through our website, Products, or the related services provided solely by ReqCloud. This Privacy Policy applies only to the use and disclosure of Personal Data that we collect while you use our website, Products, or related services.

Our provision of a link to any other website or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. When you click on such a link, you will leave our site and go to another site. During this process, a third party may collect Personal Data or Anonymous Data from you.

We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for, these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of this Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites or content, or to any collection of data after you click on a link to a third party. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

Use of Your Personal Data

In general, Personal Data you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. ReqCloud uses your Personal Data in the following ways: to facilitate the creation of and secure your account on our network; identify you as a user in our system; provide improved administration of our website, Products, and related services; improve the quality of experience when you interact with our website, Products, and related services; send you a welcome e-mail to verify ownership of the e-mail address provided when your account was created; send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories; respond to your inquiries related to employment opportunities or other requests; send job applicant information; send promotional communications; provide you with hardcopy or electronic newsletters, or surveys; send upgrades and special offers related to our Products and related services and for other marketing purposes of ReqCloud, should you request to receive such communications from us; make telephone calls to you, from time to time, as a part of secondary fraud protection or to solicit your feedback.

We may create Anonymous Data records from Personal Data by excluding information (such as your name) that make the data personally identifiable to you. We use this Anonymous Data to analyze request and usage patterns so that we may enhance the content of our Products and services and improve site navigation. ReqCloud reserves the right to use for other purposes and to disclose Anonymous Data to third parties in its discretion.

If you provide feedback on any of our Products or related services to us, we may use such feedback for any purpose, provided we will not associate such feedback with your Job Data or your Personal Data. ReqCloud will collect any information contained in such communication and will treat the Job Data and Personal Data in such communication in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Disclosure of Your Personal Data

We may share your Personal Data with third parties to provide technical support or to provide specific services, such as hosting of your applications, communicating with you via live chat software or payment processing for purchases.

Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Data (as described below), ReqCloud may disclose Personal Data if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on ReqCloud; or (b) protect or defend the rights or property of ReqCloud or users of the Products or related services.

If ReqCloud is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

Except as otherwise stated in this policy, we do not sell, trade, share, or rent the Personal Data collected from our services to third parties other than as outlined in this policy. You expressly consent to the sharing of your Personal Data as described in this policy.

Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Data

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Data. We will periodically send you free newsletters and e-mails that directly promote the use of our site or the purchase of our Products or services. When you receive newsletters or promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below). Should you decide to opt-out of receiving future mailings, we may share your e-mail address with third parties to ensure that you do not receive further communications from third parties. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you notices of any updates to our Terms of Service or Privacy Policy.

You may change any of your Personal Data in your account by editing your profile within the registration portion of our website or by sending an e-mail to us at the e-mail address set forth below. You may request deletion of your account information by us by sending an email to info@reqcloud.com, but please note that we may be required (by law or otherwise) to keep this information and not delete it (or to keep this information for a certain time, in which case we will comply with your deletion request only after we have fulfilled such requirements). When we delete account information, it will be deleted from the active database, but may remain in our archives. We will otherwise retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services as well as is necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

Advertising

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you targeted ads, you may opt-out by clicking here.

Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our web site which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us at info@reqcloud.com.

Social Media Features and Widgets

Our Web site includes Social Media Integration Features, such as the job posts to LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook, Google, and other services and other interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

Information Related to Data Collected for our Clients

ReqCloud processes information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. ReqCloud works with its Clients to help them provide notice to their customers concerning, the purpose for which personal information is collected.

We collect personally identifiable information such as first and last name, phone number, zip code, e-mail address, professional title, company name, and password from our Customers along with another other personal information furnished via connected Social Media accounts by LinkedIn, Twitter, Facebook, and Google.

We use this information to respond to requests that you make, or to aid us in serving you better. ReqCloud uses your Personal Data in the following ways: to facilitate the creation of and secure your account on our network; identify you as a user in our system; provide improved administration of our website, Products, and related services; improve the quality of experience when you interact with our website, Products, and related services; send you a welcome e-mail to verify ownership of the e-mail address provided when your account was created; send you administrative e-mail notifications, such as security or support and maintenance advisories; send promotional communications; provide you with hardcopy or electronic newsletters, or surveys; send upgrades and special offers related to our Products and related services and for other marketing purposes of ReqCloud, should you request to receive such communications from us; make telephone calls to you, from time to time, as a part of secondary fraud protection or to solicit your feedback.

ReqCloud collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. ReqCloud works with its Clients to help them provide notice to their customers concerning, the purpose for which personal information is collected.

Choice

We collect information for our clients, if you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the client that you interact with directly. If you are a Client and would like to update your account please email us at info@reqcloud.com.

Access to Data Controlled by our Clients

ReqCloud has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes nor does it store the information provided to the Customer. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the ReqCloud's Client (the data controller). If the Client requests ReqCloud to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

Types of Job Data We Collect

ReqCloud collects Job Data on clients' behalf when clients request for their Applicant Tracking Systems (ATS) to be connected to the ReqCloud systems with the purposes of automatically importing job related data. Job information may also be entered into the ReqCloud system manually by clients. Additionally, job applicants may submit job applications in response to jobs posted by ReqCloud clients. "Job Data" means data related to all such job-related imported data, manual job postings, and job applications.

Use of Your Job Data

Job Data we collect is primarily used to allow clients with job marketing and recruitment processes. ReqCloud may aggregate Job Data across multiple accounts and use this data to create and publish industry benchmarks or comparative application performance metrics. You also have the option of disabling collection of certain types of Job Data collected through our Products and services, which you may exercise by following the instructions for the applicable Product or service.

Disclosure of Your Job Data

We may share your Job Data with third parties to provide technical support or to provide specific services.

We may enter into agreements with Partner Companies. A Partner Company may want access to Job Data that we collect from its customers. As a result, we may provide your Job Data to a Partner Company on a confidential basis in order assist the Partner Company in providing customer support. Because we do not control the privacy practices of our Partner Companies, you should read and understand their privacy policies.

ReqCloud may disclose Job Data if it believes in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on ReqCloud; or (b) protect or defend the rights or property of ReqCloud or users of the Products or related services.

If another company acquires our company or our assets, that company will possess the Job Data collected by it and us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Job Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

Except as otherwise stated in this policy, we do not disclose the Job Data collected from our services to third parties without consent from you. You expressly consent to the sharing of your Job Data as described in this policy.

Security of Your Application and Personal Data

ReqCloud is committed to protecting the security of your Job Data and Personal Data. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Job Data and Personal Data from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We also require you to enter a password to access your account information. Please do not disclose your account password to unauthorized people. Despite these measures, you should know that ReqCloud cannot fully eliminate security risks associated with Job Data and Personal Data and mistakes and security breaches may happen. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at the information below.

Contact Information

ReqCloud welcomes your comments or questions regarding this Privacy Policy. Please e-mail us at info@reqcloud.com.

Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any substantial changes in the way we use your Job Data and Personal Data, we will notify you by sending you an e-mail to the last e-mail address you provided to us and/or by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the earlier of thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an e-mail notice to you of the changes, thirty (30) calendar days following our posting of notice of the changes on our site, or the date that you accept the changes (e.g., by clicking an "I Accept" button or similar means). These changes will be effective immediately for new users of our website, Products or related services. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Data to provide us with your most current e-mail address. In the event that the last e-mail address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the e-mail containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. In any event, changes to this Privacy Policy may affect our use of Job Data or Personal Data that you provided us prior to our notification to you of the changes. If you do not wish to permit changes in our use of your Job Data or Personal Data, you must notify us prior to the effective date of the changes that you wish to deactivate your account with us. Continued use of our website, Products, or related services, following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

This Privacy Policy was last revised on September 24, 2012.
